#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lam-nguyen-a9a25a74 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Terraform

.NET

**Entity Framework** 

### Languages

English (Professional Working)
Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer (MCSD)

AWS Certified Solutions Architect - Associate

# Lam Nguyen

Senior DevOps Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

## Summary

With more than 10 years of experience in software development as a developer, I have a proven ability to convey concepts and bring ideas to life by coupling my programming expertise with good communication skills.

My experience includes developing cross-browser and crossplatform compatible solutions with the latest technologies.

I have worked closely with clients from Europe to understand their requirements, business logic for technology products/applications.

### Highlight skills

- .NET framework, NET core
- ASP.NET/ASP.NET Core MVC/Web API
- Entity Framework
- C#, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- Microsoft SQL server, MongoDB
- Performance Analysis / Profiling
- Message queue (RabbitMQ), Redis cache
- Amazon Web Services (AWS)
- DevOps, Docker, CI/CD. ELK stack, Linux, Ansible, Terraform
- Source control (github/bitbucket)
- System architecture / Design pattern / SOLID principles
- Scrum / Agile / Jira

## Experience

Axon Active - Agile Offshore Software Development Company DevOps Engineer

November 2020 - Present (4 years 5 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Conexus Senior Software Engineer January 2018 - November 2020 (2 years 11 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Orient Software Development
Software Developer
February 2012 - January 2018 (6 years)
Suite 5.8, 5th Floor, E.Town Building, 364 Cong Hoa Street, HCMC

## Education

Ho Chi Minh University of Foreign Language and Information Technology

Bachelor's Degree, Information Technology · (2007 - 2011)